Julian Kennon Software Engineer j@juliankennon.com 408.836.2785 juliankennon.com github.com/julianken

Hello

I'm Julian, a Software Engineer currently based out of Bend, Oregon. I specialize in front end development, but have significant experience in full stack development. My experience gives me a wide understanding of software development, as well as a specialized, always evolving knowledge of the front end. I am also highly adaptable, and am able to learn and implement new technologies when needed.

Proficiencies

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, JavaScript, Node, Ember, is, Ruby on Rails, Linux, PHP5, Sketch 3, MySQL, Express, MongoDB

Experience

Selz.com **Revision Agency**

Bend, OR (Remote) Los Angeles, CA (Remote) Front End Developer Full-Stack Developer July 2017 - Present Aug. 2016 - July 2017

Vuria Creative Freelance

SF/Portland/Phoenix Phoenix, AZ Front-End Developer Full-Stack Developer Oct. 2015 - Aug. 2016 May 2015 - Present

San Francisco Superior Court United States Army Reserve

San Francisco, CA USA Legal Intern Sergeant

Dec. 2013 - Jun. 2014 Apr. 2009 - Apr. 2016

Education San Francisco State University

DeAnza College San Francisco, CA Cupertino, CA B.A. Political Science A.A. Liberal Arts Jan. 2012 - May 2014 May 2009 - Dec. 2012 Julian Software Engineer julian.kennon.d@gmail.com 408.836.2785

Selz.com

Create and update UI elements for dashboard.

Bend, OR (Remote)

Manage all themes and styles.

Front End Developer

Created and managed Help portal - help.selz.com.

July 2017 - Present

Involved directly in design decisions and discussions.

Responsible for testing all releases.

Timely bug fixes and user support.

Revision Agency Los Angeles, CA (Remote) Full-Stack Developer Aug. 2016 - July 2017 Developed, deployed, QA'd and maintained Web applications for clients.

Discussed, planned and developed features.

Deployed APIs, front-end applications, and traditional full stack applications.

Worked with Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, Express, Laravel, and Emberjs.

Worked with JWT tokens for user authentication from API to front-end application.

DevOps with DigitalOcean, Ubuntu 14.04, 16.04, and Debian Linux.

Vuria Creative

Phoenix, AZ

Full-Stack Developer

Oct. 2015 - Aug. 2016

Developed, deployed, QA'd and maintained Web applications using

PHP

Laravel

MySQL

Gulp

¡Query/Javascript

HTML/CSS

iOS (Objective C)

Vagrant

Debian Linux